[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what time of the day is the traditional Chinese meal called You tiao usually eaten?", "correct_answer": "Morning", "incorrect_answers": ["Afternoon", "Evening", "Lunch"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the word kangaroo according to legend?", "correct_answer": "I dont understand you.", "incorrect_answers": ["I dont know.", "Look at this!", "What is this?"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which film does the following quote come from?\nHey, I think I ran over some - I think I ran over a wookie back there on the expressway...", "correct_answer": "THX 1138", "incorrect_answers": ["Star Wars V: The Empire Strikes Back", "Star Wars II: Attack of the Clones", "Caravan of Courage: An Ewok Adventure"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the gestation period of a rhino?", "correct_answer": "16 months", "incorrect_answers": ["12 months", "20 months", "24 months"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which famous 19th century author had the pen-name Boz?", "correct_answer": "Charles Dickens", "incorrect_answers": ["Mark Twain", "Bozzie Haversham", "Daniel Defoe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not one of the four main parts that make up a prescription?", "correct_answer": "petition", "incorrect_answers": ["signature", "inscription", "subscription"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Oliver Rose do to the fish his wife has prepared for her guests in the 1989 dark comedy movie The War of the Roses?", "correct_answer": "He urinates on it.", "incorrect_answers": ["He blows his nose in a tissue and throws it in the fish.", "He sprinkles it with a laxative powder.", "He feeds it to his dog."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor delivered this roguish line in a noted Civil War movie that premiered in 1939?  ...and you Miss, are no lady.", "correct_answer": "Clark Gable", "incorrect_answers": ["Lionel Barrymore", "Spencer Tracy", "Humphrey Bogart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not a function of the circulatory system?", "correct_answer": "Excretion of unwanted substances", "incorrect_answers": ["Stabilizing body temperature", "Maintaing pH", "Transport of vital substances"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Blue Senate Guards, that first appear in Star Wars: Episode 1, are armed with what?", "correct_answer": "Blaster Rifles", "incorrect_answers": ["Force Pikes", "Swords", "Grenade Launchers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these actors/actresses did not star in the movie Earthquake?", "correct_answer": "Fred Astaire", "incorrect_answers": ["Lorne Greene", "Charlton Heston", "Ava Gardner"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is a widespread myth that vegetarians cannot provide this to their body, because it could only be supplied from meat. However, it is found in soy, beans, nuts, milk, cheese, eggs, etc.", "correct_answer": "Protein", "incorrect_answers": ["Calories", "Vitamins", "Minerals"]}]